Guide to the Yale University Films Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Films and clips produced by University Public Information, circa 1978; Accession 1990-A-068
  - The Black West: Application and Budgets, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 373 - 375)
  - "Blacks in the Military", 1983 (Box 11, Folder 376)
  - "Loyalists" Project Application, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 377)
  - "A More Perfect Union"
    - 896A-53-44737, February-July 1983 (Box 11, Folder 378)
    - Application, National Endowment for the Humanities 896A-53-44737, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 379)
    - Application, National Endowment for the Humanities, Supplemental Budget 896A-53-44739, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 380)
    - Constitution Supplemental Budget, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 381)
  - Notes and Correspondences896A-53-44737 GN 20885.83, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 382)
  - Production Schedule and Budget Detail Breakdowns 896A-53-44737, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 383)
  - Copyrights, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Chris Spotted EagleThe Great Spirit Within the Hole, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - ConnecticutHumanities Council:Whose Rights Are These AnywayPreliminary Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 386 - 387)
  - ConnecticutHumanities Council: "Greeting the Message to the Media and Others", undated (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - FMC Corporation, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - National Health, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 391)
  - Handicapped, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Lionheart, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - Media Design Studios
    - Distribution Agreements, 1982-1981 (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Distribution Rejections, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 397)
    - Faith Hubley Distribution, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 398)
    - Federal Tax Reports, Forms and Information, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - TV Yale-New Haven Educational Corporation, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Yale Films Distribution, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - National Black Programming Consortium, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Guidelines, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 403 - 404)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Orwell Project, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Pacifica, undated (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Ratings Data, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Stalin: National Endowment for the Humanities: Application, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Subscriptions and Publications, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - Searcginger, Gene: Budget for Henri Nouwen Film, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - Syndicators, undated (Box 11, Folder 413)
  - Selznick, Daniel Mayer, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 414)
  - Foundation Underwriting, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 415 - 416)
  - Corporate Underwriters, Minority Interests, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Foundations, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Foundation Information, 1977-1984 (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Journey to the Next: Invoices, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Telephone, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Office Equipment: Miscellaneous, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Office Machines: Owner's Manuals, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Office Machines: Standing Orders and Purchasing Information, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Photocopiers, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Typewriters, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Film Festivals, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Archive Inventory, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Film Inventories, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Insurance, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Cast Insurance Claim, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Errors and Omissions Correspondence: Pinkerton, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Autism Film: Release Rights Signed, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Preview Requests and Reponses, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - 896A-53-25575: Endowment, Bills and Requisitions (lacking), 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - 896A-53-25575: Statement Analyses, Endowment, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - 896A-53-25575: Personnel, Endowment, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - 896A-53-25575: Notes and Correspondence, Endowment, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - SiringoInformation, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Boswell-National Endowment for the Humanities
    - Standing and Personnel, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Cleared, Assets, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 443)
    - Statements Analysis, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - Boswell, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities-BoswellCorrespondence, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - BoswellDistribution, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Public Broadcasting System Guidelines, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - BoswellCorrespondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 449)
  - Reid Script, Recorded, 1981 July 9 (Box 12, Folder 450)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Spending Analysis, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 451)
  - Howard's Trip to Scotland, 1981 October (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Yale Archives, 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 454)
  - Articles about the Media Design Studio, 1975-1982 (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - MBCSDK: "That's Hollywood" Richard NathanLicense Agreement for Footage, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Distribution Report Forms, undated (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - "The Development of American Law" Sent Dec 20, 1988 to Annenberg/Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - "An Aging America", Sent to Annenberg/Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting Submission on Sep 8, 1988 "The Life and Times of Joseph Stalin" (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - CPB Submitted Apr 24, 1987 "The Life and Times of Joseph Stalin" (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Comments Re: Mar 1987 Submission of "Stalin" (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - "The Life and Times of Joseph Stalin", National Endowent for the Humanities Mar 20, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - "Enewetak", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1989 September (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - "Enewetak", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1986 September 12 (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - "A More Perfect Union", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1986 May (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - "Stalin", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1986 March 20 (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - "Stalin", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1986 March 20 (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Script of "Hotel Bello" by David Pownall, R/C, undated (Box 13, Folder 469)
  - "Roosevelt and Churchill", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 470)
  - "Random Walk Down Wall St.", 1985 May (Box 13, Folder 471)
  - "Roosevelt and Churchill", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1985 April (Box 13, Folder 472)
  - "Roosevelt and Churchill", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1985 January (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - Bill's Revision of Rasky's Script, undated (Box 13, Folder 474)
  - Original Script Submitted by Harry Rasky, RandC, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 475)
  - Boswell for the Defence: Supplemental(for Public Television Broadcast), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 476)
  - Cassidy: Twentieth-Century Fox Contract, 1969-1982 (Box 13, Folder 477)
  - Cassidy: Writers Guild, 1970-1976 (Box 13, Folder 478)
  - Universal Studios, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - Twentieth Century Fox, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 480)
  - Cassidy/Text, 1969-1975 (Box 13, Folder 481)
  - Paul Newman:Butch Cassidy, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 482)
  - Cassidy: Screen Actors Guild, 1970-1975 (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - NBC International, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 484)
  - Copyright/Cassidy, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 485)
  - Robert Crawford/Cassidy, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 486)
  - Laboratory Elements, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 487)
  - Insurance,Cassidy, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 488)
  - Paid Invoices,Cassidy, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - IATSE Agreements,Cassidy, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - CassidyNBC, 1964-1976 (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - FlorenceSmall, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - Anticipated Funds Clearing Account: 87999, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - General, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 494)
  - Faberge,Cassidy, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Directors Guild of America,Cassidy, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - EYR Campus Programs Distribution, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 497)
  - Butch CassidyRoyalties, 1975-1985 (Box 14, Folder 498)
  - Cassidy/Cast/Crew, undated (Box 14, Folder 499)
  - "Westering" Series Proposal, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 500)
  - Siringo: Production, Personnel, etc., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 501)
  - "We All Have Tales", 1981 (Box 14, Folder 502)
  - Exceptionalities, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 503)
  - Monologues, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 504)
  - Siringo: ExternalWest Pend: Permanent, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 505)
  - SiringoRelated Correspondence and Projections: Replaced Projections and Budgets, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 506)
  - Sources, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 507)
  - Day Player Contracts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 508)
  - Day Player Contracts, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 509)
  - CaliforniaUnemployment Claims, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 510)
  - CaliforniaTax Reports, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 511)
  - Screen Actors Guild Information, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 512)
  - Screen Actors Guild ReportsSiringo, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 513)
  - Directors Guild Correspondence, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 514)
  - Directors Guild of America Reports, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 515)
  - Directors Guild of America: Report Forms and Information, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - CaliforniaTax Information, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 517)
  - Western States Sales Tax Information, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 518)
  - 1099s: Information, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 519)
  - Media Design Studio Productions: Payroll, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 520)
  - Media Design Studio Productions: Formation, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 521)
  - Postponed Payments, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 522)
  - Loss and Damage:Siringo, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 523)
  - Media Design Studio Productions: Summary by Vendor, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 524 - 525)
  - Summary of Location Cash Expenses forSiringo, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 526)
  - "After the Eye of the Storm": Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 527)
  - "This Generation": Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 528)
  - "Love Letters to the World", 1984 (Box 15, Folder 529 - 530)
  - "Autobiography", 1984 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - "A More Perfect Union", 1984 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - "The Black West" Original/ Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - "The Black West", Jun, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - "The Great Argument: Slavery and Antislavery", Prepared for National Endowment for the Humanities but not Submitted, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Loyalists, Jan, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Orwell: National Endowment for the Humanities Application, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Orwell: Corporation for Public Broadcasting Application, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - "The Great Argument: Slavery and Antislavery", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - "The Great Argument: Slavery and Antislavery", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 540)
  - "Stalin", National Endowment for the Humanities, July 1983 (Box 15, Folder 541)
  - "Stalin", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 542)
  - "A More Perfect Union": National Endowment for the Humanities Division of Education, June 28, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 543)
  - "Stalin", National Endowment for the Humanities, December 1982 (Box 15, Folder 544)
  - "A More Perfect Union", National Endowment for the Humanities, early 1982 (Box 15, Folder 545)
  - "A More Perfect Union", Corporation for Public Broadcasting, April 1982 (Box 15, Folder 546)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Re: London Journal, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 547)
  - "The Great Argument: Slavery and Antislavery", National Endowment for the Humanities, November 1981 (Box 15, Folder 548)
  - "A More Perfect Union", National Endowment for the Humanities, July 1981 (Box 15, Folder 549)
  - "Olmstead", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Language Project, National Endowment for the Humanities, May 1978 (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Boswell(Reid, "The Sheep Stealer"), National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - "Reid, the Sheep Stealer"Universityof Pittsburgh/MediaDesign Studio Subcontract, National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 553)
  - "Westering", National Endowment for the Humanities Jun 1, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - "Westering", National Endowment for the Humanities Feb 12, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 555)
  - "History of the West", National Endowment for the Humanities Jan, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Lilly Endowment: Piaget, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - 20th Century Fox: "Marigolds", 1972-1977 (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - "Creation of a Character" Project, 1978-1983 (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - "Creation of a Character" Film: Moon Marigolds, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 560)
  - "Slaughter House"
    - Soundtrack, Rights/Release, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 561)
    - Distribution, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 562)
    - Participation Crawford, D00B, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 563)
    - Drafts, undated (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Vonnegut/Geller Screenwriter, undated (Box 16, Folder 565)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Grant R60-34-16: Film and Video Artists in Residence, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 566)
  - "Slaughterhouse"
    - Artwork, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 567)
    - Copyright and Budget, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 568)
    - Music, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 569)
    - Crew List, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 570)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 571)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 572)
  - Miscellaneous: "Waldo", "Marigold",Butch CassidyCorrespondence, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 573)
  - "Waldo", 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 575)
  - Film: Films Incorporated: "The Making ofButch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid", 1969-1977 (Box 16, Folder 576)
  - Films, Inc.: Expanded Cinema, undated (Box 16, Folder 577)
  - George Roy Hill/CassidyCorrespondence, 1969-1977 (Box 16, Folder 578)
  - Films, Inc.: "Creation of a Character", undated (Box 16, Folder 579)
  - Films, Inc.:Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid, 1973-1979 (Box 16, Folder 580)
  - Films, Inc.: Catalog for Home Video Operations, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 581)
  - 896A-53-87411:Butch CassidySTMTs, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 582)
  - 896A-53-87411:Butch CassidyDistribution not cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - 896A-53-87411:Butch CassidyDistribution cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - STMTs, for "Slaughterhouse", "Marigolds", IQDC, "Cockaboody" (lacking), undated (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - 896G-53-87411 General Distribution not cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - 896G-53-87411 General Distribution cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Applications for National Endowment for the Humanities Education Division: "A More Perfect Union", 1983 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - "A More Perfect Union", National Endowment for the Humanties Education Jul 1, $266,920 Grant, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Transfers: Advances Outstanding, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - ProgramCenter: Correspondence and Projections, 1975-1979 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - "Strangers in the Family" Budget and STMT Analysis: Connecticut Humanities Council, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - "Strangers in the Family" Discretionary Files, Grant/Notes: Connecticut Humanities Council, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - "Strangers" Bills and Requisitions: Connecticut Humanities Council, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - "Strangers" Project Information and Agreement: Connecticut Humanities Council, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - 896A-53-87152, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 596)
  - 896C-E-53-87152, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 597)
  - 896K,M-53-87152, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 598)
  - 896P-U-53-87152 (lacking), 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 599)
  - 896B-53-57096Van Gogh Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 600)
  - The New "A More Perfect Union": Sent to National Endowment for the Humanities 2/10/82, 1981 December 7 (Box 17, Folder 601)
  - Yale Media Design Studio National Endowment for the Humanities Proposal PO#743202: TYCO W/Budget, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 602)
  - "A Random Walk Down Wall Street", Description, undated (Box 17, Folder 603)
  - "Wall Street", Proposals and Reactions, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 604)
  - "This Generation" Project, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 605)
  - "This Generation" Applications and Funding, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 606)
  - "Stalin": National Endowment for the Humanities, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 607)
  - 87152-past "Stalin" Project, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 608)
  - "Stalin" Budget: Mar, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 609)
  - "Stalin" National Endowment for the Humanities Proposal and Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 610)
  - "A More Perfect Union" Budget, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 611)
  - Constitution Endorsements, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 612)
  - "A More Perfect Union", National Endowment for the Humanities, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 613)
  - Constitution Marketing, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 614)
  - Constitution Education, Budget and Proposal, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 615)
  - WHYY Philadelphia, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - "Stalin" Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 617)
  - Roosevelt/Churchill, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 618)
  - WETA, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 619)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: "The Great Argument", 1986 (Box 17, Folder 620)
  - Proposal Guides, 1975-1987 (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Annenberg, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Resumes, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - New Board, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Study Guides, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Film Studies' Programs: Important Letters, 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - RWS Loyalist Draft, undated (Box 18, Folder 627)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 628)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 629)
  - Endorsements for Constituiton Project, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 630)
  - State Governors, Federal and Bicentennial Commissions, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 631)
  - Constitution: Funding, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 632)
  - "The Great Argument: Slavery or Antislavery", 1979-1986 (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - "The Great Argument", 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - "A Random Walk Down Wall Street", 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 635)
  - A Class Divided, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 636)
  - A Class Divided: Publicity, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - A Class Divided: Feature Film, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - Enewetak, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - Law Resumes: Commitment, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - Funding: Law, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - The Development of American Law: Panelists Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - Law: Proposal to Annenberg, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - Law: Lawrence Friedman, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - Responses From Professors, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 645)
  - Law: Replies From Professors, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 646)
  - Letter to Professors, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 647)
  - Law: Resumés, undated (Box 18, Folder 648)
  - Names/Addresses of Law Advisory Panel, undated (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - American Bar Association, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 650)
  - KQED, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 651)
  - 2-Year College Representatives, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - Brandeis: Law, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 653)
  - North Carolina, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 654)
  - QuinnipiacCollege, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 656)
  - Public Broadcasting System Adult Learning, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 657)
  - The Annenberg/Corporation for Public Broadcasting Project: Telecourse Utilization Survey: Austin Community College, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 658)
  - Other: Law, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 659)
  - Law: Formative Evaluation, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 660)
  - Law: Instructional Design, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - An Aging America: Panelists, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 662)
  - Aging Funding, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - An Aging America: Annenberg/Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 664)
  - Aging: Resumés, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 665)
  - Names, Addresses of Aging Advisory Panel, undated (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - Responses from Aging Scholars, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - Aging: Outstanding Correspondence, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Aging: Robert Butler, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - Telecourse Consortia, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Aging: Formative Evaluation, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 671)
  - Aging: Instructional Design, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 672)
  - Aging: Notes form Meetings Re: Annenberg Submission, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 673)
  - Aging: Outlines, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 674)
  - Autobiography, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 675)
  - Embryonic Projects not taken: Byrd, Hess, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 676)
  - Huey Long, undated (Box 19, Folder 677)
  - Beaumont, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 678)
  - Children Arts Series: National Endowment for the Arts/Getty, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 679)
  - The Black West, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 680)
  - Young Victories, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 681)
  - Documentation forRoosevelt and ChurchillRe-submission; Endorsements ofSuddenly an Eagle, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - As Others See Us, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 683)
  - Constitution: Annenberg, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 684)
  - Constitution: Editing Division (?), 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Whose Rights Are These Anyway?, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - Robert Louis Stevenson, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - "Stalin": Drafts, Proposal, Chronology, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 688)
  - "Stalin", 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 689)
  - Strangers in a Family, 1981-1986 (Box 19, Folder 690)
  - Orwell, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 691)
  - U.S., British Health Systems, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 692)
  - School Violence: Corporal Punishment, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 693)
  - David Apter: Japan Project, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 694)
  - American Bar Association Series, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 695)
  - Van Gogh, 1979-1985 (Box 19, Folder 696)
  - First Amendment, 1979-1985 (Box 19, Folder 697)
  - Immigration, undated (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - Eye of the Beholder, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 699)
  - Irvin Child, 1965-1981 (Box 19, Folder 700)
  - Newman/Woodward, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 701)
  - "Stalin": Manya's and Jerry's, undated (Box 19, Folder 702)
  - Foreign Policy, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 703)
  - Non-profit Project, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 704)
  - Language Project, 1978-1982 (Box 20, Folder 705)
  - Metamorphosis, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 706)
  - Olmsted, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 707)
  - Museum Tour: Captioning, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 708)
  - Moral Heroes, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 709 - 710)
  - Mike Hoover, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 711)
  - Artificial Intelligence, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 712)
  - Sports History, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 713)
  - History of the West Proposal:SiringoProposal, undated (Box 20, Folder 714)
  - Language: Annenberg, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 715)
  - Loyalists: Reading List, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Loyalists: Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Loyalists: Source Information, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Loyalists Proposal: Clips Used, undated (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Loyalist Readings not Used, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Loyalist Project/Rivington DABArticles, Joseph Brant, undated (Box 20, Folder 721)
  - Loyalist Scripting Proposal: BP's Drafts, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 722)
  - Loyalists: Scholars Comments on RWS Party, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 723)
  - Loyalist Good Stuff, undated (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - Loyalist Rewrite Tidbits: Content Outline, undated (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - Mike Hoover Stuff, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - Bowen, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - Loyalists: Winer, undated (Box 20, Folder 728)